{
    "subject": "resource/Goodfellas",
    "predicate": "property/editing",
    "object": "resource/Thelma_Schoonmaker",
    "human_readable": "Goodfellas was edited by Thelma Schoonmaker.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.885991632938385,
            "question": "Was Thelma Schoonmaker nominated for any awards for her work on Goodfellas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8509964942932129,
            "question": "Which movie did Thelma Schoonmaker edit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8265120387077332,
            "question": "Has Thelma Schoonmaker worked on other films besides Goodfellas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8203626871109009,
            "question": "Who edited the film Goodfellas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7645354270935059,
            "question": "Is Thelma Schoonmaker a film editor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5936837792396545,
            "question": "What is Thelma Schoonmaker known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4737914204597473,
            "question": "What is the name of the film director who collaborated with Thelma Schoonmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4267272353172302,
            "question": "What is notable about Thelma Schoonmaker's work in filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4054248631000519,
            "question": "What year was the film Goodfellas released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35052016377449036,
            "question": "What genre is the movie Goodfellas?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Goodfellas was edited by Thelma Schoonmaker.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7903_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Goodfellas released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7903_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is notable about Thelma Schoonmaker's work in filmmaking?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7903_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film director who collaborated with Thelma Schoonmaker?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7903_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7903_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7903_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7903_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7903_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7903_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7903_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7903_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7903_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7903_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7903_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that the triple \"Goodfellas was edited by Thelma Schoonmaker\" is supported.\n\nHere is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple instances of text that explicitly mention Thelma Schoonmaker's involvement in editing Goodfellas, including:\n\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7903/re-ranker-msmarco/41.txt\n* \"She won an Oscar for her editing work on Raging Bull and Thelma Schoonmaker has edited each of Martin Scorsese's movies since. She also won the Oscar for The Aviator and was nominated for Gangs of New York and Goodfellas.\"\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7903/re-ranker-msmarco/67.txt\n* \"started working with Scorsese on his debut feature film, Who's That Knocking at My Door (1967), and has edited all of his films since Raging Bull (1980). She has also been nominated eleven times for the BAFTA Award for Best Editing, winning for Raging Bull and Goodfellas (1990).\"\n\nThese instances provide strong evidence that Thelma Schoonmaker was indeed involved in editing Goodfellas."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents support the statement that \"Goodfellas was edited by Thelma Schoonmaker,\" as multiple documents mention her extensive collaboration with Martin Scorsese, including editing his films such as Goodfellas."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}